Jiming,
Wen Shiyi has been arrested.
Thank you.
Now that my revenge is complete,
I feel so relieved.
Was she
really arrested?
Xiaoyu.
Jiming,
you betrayed me.
You betrayed our relationship.
I didn't.
I'm going to light it.
Okay.
Do you really think
he will take Wen Shiyi to turn himself in?
You betrayed me.
I didn't.
Yes,
I used underhanded means,
and I'm cruel.
But everything I've done,
is for whom?
Is it for myself?
Lin Muyun,
he only cares about his dead ex-wife
and his illegitimate son Wang Jiming.
When did he ever
give us a second glance?
If I hadn't fought
and clawed my way,
we'd have been left
with nothing by now.
I paved the way for you,
cleared obstacles,
and helped you reach the top.
Isn't this
what all mothers would do
in the world?
I... I...
I just did it in my way.
My son.
Jiming.
I know I was wrong.
I really regret it.
Son.
For the sake of my 30 years of raising you,
I've put in a lot of efforts.
Please let me off this time.
I'll listen to you
from now on.
I'll leave today
and never come back.
Son.
Forgive me this time.
Get out.
Just forgive me this time.
Son.
Get out.
Take what you can take
and leave immediately.
What?
Never let me see you again.
Otherwise,
next time,
I will personally put you in jail.
Okay.
Son,
I didn't expect
you're still so easy to trick.
What?
Wen Shiyi ran away.
He chose to let go of the woman who ruined him
but also made him.
Is it filial piety?
Is it foolishness?
Is it residual love?
Perhaps it's just a 30-year bond
that has become an instinct etched in the bones.
Compared to hatred,
it's even harder to sever.
This fountain pen
has always been with me.
I'll give it to you.
Why?
I'll tell you later.
I'm leaving.
You go your way,
and I'll go mine.
Why did you let her go?
I...
She killed my husband,
killed my child,
and turned you into a puppet stealing others' lives.
How could you let this devil
just walk away?
I really intended to take her to turn herself in.
But
she's my mom.
Do you understand?
I don't.
Lin Jiming,
you've disappointed me.
Xintian,
trust me this once.
There's no trust left between us.
From now on,
we are
no longer a couple.
Wen Shiyi has escaped.
Before she escaped,
she must have transferred as much money as possible.
All the money that hasn't been transferred,
and destroyed all the evidence.
I need you to use
all your audit permissions
to find out her last money flow.
Find out
the evidence she may not have had time to erase.
I need the highest level key
and the internal authorization of the audit committee.
It takes time,
and my brother's help.
And
it's risky.
Only when Wen Shiyi is arrested,
you and your brother can be safe.
This is the only common goal
we have now.
I understand.
I'll think of a way
to get my brother's help.
Mr. Wen,
this place
is absolutely safe.
I bought it years ago
through a proxy.
Xu,
I'm sorry to bother you.
You're welcome.
As for the funds,
they've been transferred in batches
through the usual channels.
I can guarantee it's clean.
It's just that the thing you asked
took a little more effort.
Please take a look.
These are
emails between Lin Jiming and Guan Tiantian
in their tone.
These few
point to their
fuzzy fund flow.
This is a draft of a confession.
It says that
the two of them conspired to frame you
with the intention of swallowing up the Lin Group.
The most important thing
is the fingerprint on the back.
Lin Jiming's?
Yes.
Well done.
Xu
Find some media with a keen sense of smell
and send these gifts anonymously.
The headlines should be eye-catching.
The stories should be sensational.
Tomorrow morning,
I want the headlines all over the city to be
the wonderful drama
of the unfilial son of the Lin family
and the avenging woman.
Mr. Lin, Mr. Lin.
Mr. Lin, what's your response
to the front-page report
that you and Lawyer Guan
conspired to frame Chairman Wen?
Is the confession with your fingerprint on it real?
Did you know about it all along?
Is Chairman Wen's disappearance related to you?
Are you trying to take over the company?
Mr. Lin, please answer.
Mr. Lin, Mr. Lin.
Answer, Mr. Lin.
These are all malicious slander,
baseless talk.
Our Lin Group
will reserve the right to pursue legal action.
Hey, Mr. Lin, don't go.
Mr. Lin, Mr. Lin.
Don't go, Mr. Lin.
Wen Shiyi.
Fingerprint.
How did she get my fingerprint?
How is this possible?
It might be the batch of old director signature documents
you asked me to take and destroy last month.
Old director signature documents.
Director Wen.
Director Wen asked me to show it to her first.
I didn't know she would...